bankatunion.com 2019-04-16

# Privacy Policy | Personal Information | Atlantic Union Bank

## Protecting your personal and financial information is a priority at Atlantic Union Bank.

Please take time to read our Privacy Policy to understand how we collect and utilize your personal information.

* * *

Atlantic Union Bank respects the private nature of the personal financial information we collect. To provide the right products or services to you, we take appropriate precautions to restrict access to your personal information to only those teammates who need to know that information.

Atlantic Union Bank collects personal information when you:

  * Open an account or deposit money
  * Apply for a loan
  * Pay your bills
  * Use your debit card

Atlantic Union Bank is committed to using your information in a responsible manner. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards in compliance with federal regulations to protect your personal information.

As a reminder:

  * We do not sell, rent or trade your information to other businesses.
  * We safeguard your information.
  * We are committed to helping you protect your privacy.

Read the Atlantic Union Bank Privacy Notice. _(Note: Adobe Reader is required to view the privacy policy documentation.)_

How you can limit information sharing:

  * Call Atlantic Union Bank Customer Care
  * Fill out Atlantic Union Bank's Information Sharing Opt-Out Request Form below

Atlantic Union Bank will share information with our affiliates, which are other companies that we have common ownership or control. It's important to note that information about specific transactions and experience may be shared with others as permitted by the Fair Credit Reporting Act.

Take steps to protect your personal information by accessing our Security & Fraud Center.

### Information Sharing Opt-Out Request Form
